I killed Sirius Black!
He's back.
The police are continuing
with the investigation...
...into the cause
of the Millennium Bridge disaster.
Traffic has been halted
as police search for survivors.
The surrounding area remains closed.
The mayor has urged Londoners
to remain calm...
"Harry Potter."
Couple nights ago,
I could've sworn I saw a picture move.
- Really?
- Thought I was going around the twist.
- Hey, I was wondering...
- Eleven. That's when I get off.
You are talented, famous and powerful.
Everything Horace values.
Professor Slughorn is gonna try
to collect you, Harry.
I fear I may have stolen
a wondrous night from you, Harry.
She was, truthfully, very pretty, that girl.